<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Texts xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <ButtonTexts>
    <HintButtonText>Stage</HintButtonText>
    <RelocationScreen>Warp</RelocationScreen>
    <ConfirmRelocation>WARP!</ConfirmRelocation>
    <UnableToRelocate>In order to relocate you need to obtain one million (1e6) units of matter</UnableToRelocate>
    <PierceCountUpgrade>Piercing Power</PierceCountUpgrade>
    <ShotCooldown>Shooting Speed</ShotCooldown>
    <ChargeAttack>Charged Attack</ChargeAttack>
    <SpawnCooldown>Asteroids Spawning Frequency</SpawnCooldown>
    <Damage>Damage</Damage>
    <GlowingEnemiesSpawnRate>Glowing Enemies Spawn Chance</GlowingEnemiesSpawnRate>
    <ExplosivesAttacksTimeUpgrade>Explosives Attacks Duration</ExplosivesAttacksTimeUpgrade>
    <CoinMultiplier>Matter Multiplier</CoinMultiplier>
    <CoinMultiplierTimeUpgrade>Matter Multiplier Duration</CoinMultiplierTimeUpgrade>
    <DamageMultiplierTimeUpgrade>Damage Multiplier Duration</DamageMultiplierTimeUpgrade>
    <BossSpawnChance>Boss Spawn Chance</BossSpawnChance>
    <ForceField>Force Field</ForceField>
    <UltracoinSpawnChance>"Coin" Spawn Chance</UltracoinSpawnChance>
    <ScreenExplosion>Screen Explosion</ScreenExplosion>
    <Multishot>Multishot</Multishot>
  </ButtonTexts>
  <CurrencyTexts>
    <Matter>Matter</Matter>
    <Data>Data</Data>
  </CurrencyTexts>
  <StageTexts>
    <UniversalStage>There is no hint for this stage of the game. 
      They might appear in the future or you just need to go to touch grass</UniversalStage>
    <StageTexts>
      <string>Game might feel slow at the start, but progress will speed up as you grow.
        You could make progress faster if you use free booster located at the upper right corner
        Stage progression requirement: LvL 50 at Spawn Cooldown Upgrade.</string>
      <string>Upgrading damage might be pretty useful because you get more material from asteroids by destroying them completely
        Every 30 levels of upgrading Spawn Cooldown will cause asteroids to become more dense resulting in doubling their health and slight decreasing their amount
        The amount of material that you can obtain from them is proportional to their health, so stronger asteroids yield more material.
        Therefore, upgrading your damage becomes even more valuable as you progress further.
        You probably want to push to the Charge Attack upgrade because it's quite strong, but it is not really necessary
        Stage progression requirement: Lvl 1 at charge attack.</string>
      <string>New upgrades are now available that allow you to obtain temporary power-ups from glowing asteroids.
        Although these power-ups don't last very long, they are more useful than they may appear at first glance.
        Don't hesitate to upgrade them.
        To progress to the next stage, you must collect one million (1e6) units of matter.</string>
      <string>Now, when you went so far, you are able to Warp
        This will restart your journey and cause you to lose all your upgrades and matter
        However, upon warping, you will have access to all the data you collected during your previous journey
        This data makes new journey more efficient, but besides passive impact it can be spent on researches
        Be careful, though, as inefficient utilization of this data could make your new journey less efficient than it could be
        (though it will still be more efficient than the previous one).</string>
    </StageTexts>
    
  </StageTexts>
  <OtherTexts>
    <DataUponRelocation>Upon Warping you will recieve {0} units of data</DataUponRelocation>
    <Cost>Cost</Cost>
  </OtherTexts>
  <TimersTexts>
    <CoinMultiplierTimerText>Matter Multiplier</CoinMultiplierTimerText>
    <DamageMultiplierTimerText>Damage Multiplier</DamageMultiplierTimerText>
    <ExplosionsTimerText>Explosives Attacks</ExplosionsTimerText>
  </TimersTexts>
  <SettingsTexts>
    <SettingsTitle>Settings</SettingsTitle>
    <MusicVolume>Music Volume</MusicVolume>
    <SoundsVolume>Sounds Volume</SoundsVolume>
    <Trails>Trails</Trails>
    <Particles>Particles</Particles>
    <StarsAmount>Stars Amount</StarsAmount>
    <Language>Language</Language>
    <SafeScreen>Safe Screen</SafeScreen>
  </SettingsTexts>
</Texts>